Guide to the Artists Space Archive MSS.291
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Exhibition Files, 1973 - 2009
  - Artists Select I: Kukuli Velarde, Renny Molenaar, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Artists Select I: Li-Lan, Tony Wong, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Artists Select I: Lorraine O'Grady, Senga Nengudi, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Artists Select I: Luis Cruz Avacela, Maria Lino, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Artists Select I: Lynda Benglis, Andrew Fenner, November 20, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Artists Select I: Margo Machida, Kristine Yuki Aono, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Artists Select I: Mark Rappaport, Niki Logis, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Artists Select I: Mary Beth Edelson, Elizabeth Burke, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Artists Select I: Nancy Dwyer, Eva Sutton, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Artists Select I: Nan Goldin, Janet Stein, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Artists Select I: Paul Cadmus, Michael Bergt, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Artists Select I: Perry Bard, Leslie Fry, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Artists Select I: Renee Cox, Lyle Ashton Harris, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Artists Select I: Starn Twins, Robin Kahn, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Artists Select I: Stefani Mar, Kuo Zhong Lee, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Artists Select I: Tiffany Bell, Connie Beckley, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Artists Select I: Tom Otterness, Jane Sherry, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - The Training of a Fragile Memory: Jeanne C. Finley, Mark Alice Durant, November 20, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Potential Projects: Diane Torr, Grace Y. Williams, Julia Platt Herzberg, Katherine Warren, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - What's a Mother to Do?: Paintings by Angela Fremont, January 3, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - AIDS Forum: Tom Strider, January 4, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - AIDS Forum: Carl Tandatnick, January 25, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Artists Select II: Administrative, January 26, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Artists Select II: Alice Aycock, Sandra Lynn (Sam) Korsak, January 26, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Artists Select II: Catherine Saalfield, Carrie Mae Weems, Fred Wilson, Teresa Osa Hidalgo-de la Riva, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Artists Select II: Dotty Attie, Helene Aylon, Suzanne Horvitz, Julia Jacquette, January 26, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Artists Select II: James Luna, Brian Cripp, Rebecca Bezmore, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Artists Select II: Jason Simon, Wendy Geller, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Artists Select II: Jennifer Bartlett, David Knudsvig, Michael Bordo, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Artists Select II: Jerri Allyn, Michael Levine, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Artists Select II: Juan Sanchez, Riche Rodriguez, Miguel Martinez, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Artists Select II: Judy Pfaff, Lisa Austin, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Artists Select II: Liliana Porter, Liisa Johanna Roberts, Maria Damarse, Carlos Cardenas, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Artists Select II: Marilyn Nance, Amir Bey, Carole Byard, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Artists Select II: Marisol Escobar, Nathaniel (Tad) Wiley, Gary Dodson, Marjorie Strider, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Artists Select II: Mary Hambelton, Stephanie Rowden, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Artists Select II: Matt Mullican, Doreen McCarthy, Matthew Benedict, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Artists Select II: May Stevens, Jenny Polak, Tina Takemoto, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Artists Select II: Mike Kelley, Doug Hammett, Kelly Mason, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Artists Select II: Nancy Grossman, Jeannie (Jean) Weissglass, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Artists Select II: Peggy Ahwesh, Jennifer Todd Reeves, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Artists Select II: Polly Apflebaum, Siobhan Liddell, Tony Feher, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Artists Select II: Rimer Cardillo, Ana Tiscornia and Alberto Lastreto, January 26, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Artists Select II: Rudolf Baranik, Jim Drobnick, Tom Melins, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Artists Select II: Sandy Skolglund, Michael Daube, Rafael Sanchez, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Artists Select II: Sherry Millner, Gary Nichols, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Artists Select II: Shirley Jaffe, Barbara Zucker, Ken Aptekar, Hugh Weiss, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Artists Select II: Sylvia de Swann, Ivy Parsons, Leonard Kemp, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Artists Select II: Sydney Blum, Tony Margarucci, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Artists Select II: Szeed Taylor, Judy Jashinsky, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Artists Select II: Swon Kwon, Michael Bennett, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Artists Select II: Tony Bechara, Michael Burke, Maria Martinez, Fernando Colon, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Artists Select II: Willie Birch, Carl Robert Pope Jr., Jerald Jackson, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - AIDS Forum: Steed Taylor, February 15, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - AIDS Forum: Robert Lukasik, March 8, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Open Dialogue: Silent Dissent - The Unreported Controversy in AIDS Research (video program), March 8, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - AIDS Forum: Glen Sacks [1 of 2], March 29, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Artists Select III: Administrative, March 30, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Artists Select III: Alyson Pou, Grace Williams, Marilyn Nance, Barbara Takinawa, March 30, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Artists Select III: Andrew Ginzel, Douglass Dibble, Lise Gervais & Phil Holland, Randall Peacock, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Artists Select III: Antonio Muntadas, Rogelio Lopez Cuenca, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Artists Select III: Bette Gordon, Tim Burns, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Artists Select III: Brian Goldberg, Robert W. Reynolds, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Artists Select III: Candida Alvarez, Charles Burwell, Diogenes Ballester, Ellen Gallagher, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Artists Select III: Carrie Mae Weems, Trena Noval, Christian Walker, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Artists Select III: David Avalos, Diane Gamboa, Barbara Carrasco, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Artists Select III: Donna Dennis, Amanda Fin, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Artists Select III: Greta Gunderson, Lou Storey, China Marks, Gail Rothschild, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Artists Select III: Jack Sonenberg, Michael Phillips, Phoebe Helman, March 30, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Artists Select III: Jessica Diamond, Janice Brigers, Christopher Cantwell, 1993-1994 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Artists Select III: John Ahearn, Rigoberto Torres, Brooke Alexander, March 30, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Artists Select III: John Coplans, Editha Mesina, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Artists Select III: John Schlesinger, Doug Henders, Gordon Brawn, Deanne Sokolin, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Artists Select III: Marina Gutierrez, Kukuli Velarde, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Artists Select III: Martha Rosler, Andrea Robbins, Max Becher, Dan Wiley, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Artists Select III: Martin Wong, DAZE, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Artists Select III: Mary Miss, Cecile Abish, Brenda Miller, Patricia Sullivan, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Artists Select III: Matthew Barney, Kathleen (Katy) Schimerty, Keith Edmier, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Artists Select III: Ming Fay, Jerry Kwan, Bojo Kemperle, Pan Yu-Jen, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Artists Select III: Nina Kuo, Richard Tsao, 1993-1994 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Artists Select III: Peter Campus, Seoung Ho Cho, Hilda Daniel, Seon Goo Hwang, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Artists Select III: Rebecca Howland, Marguerite Van Cook, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Artists Select III: Ricardo Zulera, Chuck Nanney, Max Estinger, Francois Boue, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Artists Select III: Ted Kurahara, Jack Sonenberg, Bernard Kirschen Baum, Gerald Hayes, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Artists Select III: Thomas Lanigan Schmidt, Agosto Machado, Arch Connely, Adrian Kellard, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Artists Select III: Timothy Binkley, Shelly J. Smith, Eva Sutton, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Artists Select III: Ursula von Rydingsvard, John Townsend, March 30, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Tuesday Night at the Movies: "BANNED!", April 5, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Reckles Angels: Cabaret composed and performed by Nicky Paraiso, directed by Yoshiko Chuma, April 5, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - AIDS Forum: Thomas Lanigan-Schmidt (research for potential exhibition), 1992-1994 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - AIDS Forum: Larry Jens Anderson, April 19, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - AIDS Forum: Devorah Kleinman Proposal, May-June 1994 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - AIDS Forum: Jennifer Sloan, May 10, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - AIDS Forum: Kenneth Sean Golden, May 31, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - For Beauty's Sake: Barbara Zucker, June 11, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - A Terrible Beauty: Images of Conflict in Ireland - Administrative, June 11, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - A Terrible Beauty: Imates of Conflict in Ireland- Artists' Resumes, June 11, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - A Terrible Beauty: Catalogue Drafts, June 11, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - A Terrible Beauty: Correspondence, June 11, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - A Terrible Beauty: Loan Agreements Price List, June 11, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - AIDS Forum: Robert Blanchon, June 21, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - AIDS Forum: Cynthia Madansky, July 12, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Dress Code: Evans and Wong, September 10, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Selections from The Artists' File: Amsterdam, Promotional, September 10, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Selections from the Artists' File: Todd Slaughter and Snapshots [1 of 2], September 10, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Conceptual Art from the Bay Area: Administrative, Promotional, October 29, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Conceptual Art from the Bay Area: Artists' Press, Resumes, October 29, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Conceptual Art from the Bay Area: Correspondence, Financial, October 29, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Money Commission Project: Source and Correspondence, October 29, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Six Moons Over Oaxaca: Administrative, October 29, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Six Moons Over Oaxaca: Administrative, Promotional, October 29, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Six Moons Over Oaxaca: Correspondence, Etchings, 1994-1995 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Byssodomein: Raimund Kummer - Administrative, Promotional, January 28, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Byssodomein: Raimund Kummer - Correspondence, FInancial, January 28, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Byssodomein: Raimund Kummer - Customs, Shipping, January 28, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Byssodomein: Raimund Kummer - Images, Slides, January 28, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Las Americas: The Return of Martin Steel by Osvaldo Romberg [1 of 2], January 28, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Sit Down and Watch It: Video Selected by Michel Auder - Administrative, Financial, Promotional, April 19, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Sit Down and Watch It: Artists' Resumes, April 18, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Sit Down and Watch It: Correspondence, April 18, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Authors in Search of a Publisher- Reading Series Selected by Gillian McCain, April 19, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Customized Terror: Administrative, Promotional, May 20, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Customized Terror: Correspondence, May 20, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Greg Lynn: Selected by Peter Eisenman, September 16, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Somatogenics: Selected by Charlesworth. Cindy Sherman, and Laurie Simmons, September 16, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Somatogenics: Photographic Materials, September 16, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Anne Marie Jugnet: Administrative, November 11, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Anne Marie Jugnet: Correspondence, November 11, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Anne Marie Jugnet: Resumes, Selected Works, November 11, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Vincent Beaurin, November 11, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Exhibit A: Design/Writing/Research with J. Abbott Miller, January 20, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Unnaturally Yours: Selected by Willie Cole - Administrative, Promotional, January 20, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Unnaturally Yours: Selected by Willie Cole, January 20, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Mr. Dead and Mrs. Free: A History of Squat Theatre (1969-1991) Thursdays in June: Performances, Readings, Video, June 6, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Mr. Dead and Mrs. Free: Catalogue, Press Clippings, March 30, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Mr. Dead and Mrs. Free: Promotional, Correspondence Drafts, March 30, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Squat Cafe: Photographs and Video of Squat Theatre Performances, March 30, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Squat Cafe: Video From the Centre Georges Pompidou, Paris, April 3, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - A Strategy Hinted At: New Conceptual Artists- Administrative, Promotional, September 6, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - A Strategy Hinted At: Aki Fujiyoshi, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - A Strategy Hinted At: Angie Eng, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - A Strategy Hinted At: Benita Immanuel- Grosser, September 6, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - A Strategy Hinted At: Brigitte Engler, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - A Strategy Hinted At: Michael Zahn, September 6, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - A Strategy Hinted At: Mike Sale, September 6, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - A Strategy Hinted At: Neil Goldberg, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - A Strategy Hinted At: Newspaper Drafts, Promotion, September 6, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - A Strategy Hinted At: Orit Raff, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - A Strategy Hinted At: Steven Carter, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Political Advertisement: Over 40 Years of Presidential Campaign Spots- edited by Antonio Muntadas and Marshall Reese, October 28, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - A Living Testament of the Blood Fairies: Administrative, Promotional, November 9, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - A Living Testament of the Blood Fairies: Administrative, Correspondence, Press Clippings, November 9, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - A Living Testament of the Blood Fairies: Financial, November 8, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - A Living Testament of the Blood Fairies: Visual AIDS / Text Based Selections from the Archive Project (working title) - Proposal, May 24, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Jeff Francis - Cindy Sherman, December 9, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Anna Gili: Administrative, Correspondence, January 18, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Anna Gili: Photographic Materials, January 18, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Anna Gili: Press Clippings, January 18, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Anna Gili: Shipping, January 18, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Hot Coffee: Administrative, Promotional, January 18, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Hot Coffee: Exhibition Planning, January 18, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Hot Coffee: Shipping, January 18, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Ben van Berkel: Mobile Forces - Administrative, Promotional, April 12, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Ben van Berkel: Mobile Forces - Artist Information, April 12, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Ben van Berkel: Mobile Forces - Correspondence, April 12, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Station to Station: Administrative, Promotional, April 12, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Station to Station: Artists Materials, April 12, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Station to Station: Correspondence with Curators, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Station to Station: Installation, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Station to Station: Les LeVeque, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Tampering with the Reel: Administrative, Promotional, June 7, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Tampering with the Reel: Artists Materials, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Tampering with the Reel: Collective Clubhouse Project, June 7, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Tampering with the Reel: Correspondence to Artists, June 7, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Tampering with the Reel: Installation, June 7, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Tampering with the Reel: Project Descriptions, June 7, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Tampering with the Reel: Photographic Materials, June 7, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Artists Select Series: Connie Walsh, Carola Dertnig, Liza Johnson, Erika Yeomans, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - New Music at Artists Space Programmed by Harvestworks, July 9, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Permutations: Administrative, Correspondence, Installation, September 11, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Permutations: Promotional, September 11, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Permutations: Visuals, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Savor: Administrative, Promotional, September 11, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Savor: Artists Materials, September 11, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Lines of Loss: Five Emerging Artists from Mexico, Selected by Gabriel Orozco - Administrative, Developmental, November 14, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Lines of Loss: Artists' Resumes, Research, November 14, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Lines of Loss: Customs, Developmental, November 14, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Lines of Loss: Artists' Resumes, Correspondence, Photographic Materials, November 14, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Lines of Loss: Financial, Installation, Promotional, November 14, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Present Tense: The Architecture of George Ranalli [1 of 3], November 14, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Present Tense: The Architecture of George Ranalli [2 of 3], November 14, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - 4 (to) 5: Elke Lehmann, January 24, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Abstraction in Process II: Administrative, Promotional, Research, January 24, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Abstraction in Process II: Artists' Resumes and Slides, January 24, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Digital Mapping: Architecture as Media - Administrative, Correspondence, Promotional, March 28, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Digital Mapping: Curatorial Proposals, March 28, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Digitial Mapping: Hani Rashid, March 28, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Anne Gardiner's "Through the Tuplips and the Red Red Rose", May 2, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Scope: Administrative, Correspondence, Rejected Submissions, June 4, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Scope: Administrative, Promotional, Scope 1-3 Submissions Index, June 4, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Scope Summer Video Festival: Artists' Resumes, Correspondence, June 4, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Scope: Exhibition Checklist, Resumes, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Scope: Shipping, June 4, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Video Screening Selected by Marjatta Ojd, June 6, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Scope II: Administrative, Correspondence, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Scope III: Administrative, Artists' Resumes, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Scope: Open Video Calls, June 25, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - "Nearly the Solstice" Party, June 26, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Laurie Anderson: Whirlwind - Administrative, Promotional, September 19, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Laurie Anderson: Whirlwind - Correspondence [1 of 2], 1998 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Laurie Anderson: Whirlwind - Correspondence [2 of 2], 1998 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Laurie Anderson: Whirlwind - Resume, Photographs, September 19, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Laurie Anderson: Whirlwind - Jason Middlebrook Construction, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - A Pale Soft Plane: Craig Konyk, November 21, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Project Space II: Pure Productivity by Mike Wodkowski, November 21, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Scape: Administrative, November 21, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Scape: Financial, Promotional, November 21, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Scape: Edie Winograde, November 21, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Scape: Jeremy Sigler, November 21, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Scape: Jude Elizabeth Tallichet, November 21, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Scape: Lane Twitchell, November 21, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Project Scape II: Justine Kurland, December 19, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Project Space II: Denise Fasanello, February 20, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - SHY: Administrative, Financial, February 20, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - SHY: Christine Fenzl, February 20, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - SHY: Jean-Christian Bourcart, February 20, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - SHY: Kathleen M. White, February 20, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - SHY: Marina Berio, February 20, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - SHY: Nan Goldin, February 20, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - SHY: Nicholas Pages, February 20, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - SHY: Pawel Wojtasik, February 20, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - SHY: Piotr Nathan, February 20, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - SHY: Richard N. Colon, February 20, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - SHY: Ruth Marten, February 20, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - SHY: Vivienne Dick, February 20, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Project Space II: Gina Magid, March 13, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Project Space II: Randall Peacock, March 17, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Housing: Kolaton/MacDonald Studio, April 1, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Momenta Art & the Outpost Present Third Rail on Brooklyn Community Access Television, April 2, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Dexter Buell, Arthur Jafa, Judy Stevens, April 17, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Howard Goldkrand, April 17, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Stuart Hawkins, May 11, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Cold Drink: Film and Video Festival - Administrative, Promotional, June 12, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Cold Drink: Artists' Resumes, Open Video Call Sheets, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Subway to the Outside, June 12, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Family History Wall: Project Space II [Valerie Atkisson], June 30, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Abraham Ferraro & "The Knockout Artist", July 16, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - The Searchers: Eric Schnell, Michelle Elzay, Colin Hunt - Administrative, September 16, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - The Searchers: Opening Night Photographs, Artists' Slides, September 16, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Karsten - James Krejcarek, November 20, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Made Especially for You: Administrative, Promotional, November 20, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Made Especially for You: Heidie Giannotti, November 20, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Made Especially for You: Katrin Asbury, November 20, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Made Especially for You: Matthew Brannon, November 20, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Toshiko Mori: Woven Inhabitation, November 20, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - The Society for Collective Investigation, December 16, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Architecture Research Office, February 3, 2000 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Deterritorialization of Process, February 3, 2000 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Project Space II: Nathan Carter, February 3, 2000 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Dolores Zinny and Juan Maidagan, April 1, 2000 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Echo: Curated by Anne Gardiner - Iris Binor, Trisha Donnelly, Shawn King, Hajime Nakamura, April 1, 2000 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Anywhere But Here: Administrative, Promotional, June 1, 2000 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Anywhere But Here: Artists' Resumes [1 of 2], June 1, 2000 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Anywhere But Here: Artists' Resumes [2 of 2], June 1, 2000 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - D'Nell Larson, June 1, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Transitional Home, June 1, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Project Space II: Paul Sahre, June 5, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Uri Tzaig: Duel - Administrative, Promotional, September 9, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Uri Tzaig: Duel - Catalogue & Correspondence, September 9, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Uri Tzaig: Duel - Potential Travel, Promotional, September 9, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Edward Tufte: Visual Explanations - Prints and Sculptures, November 11, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - LAB: Jenny Althoff & Alexander Vaindorf, Isabel Chang, Kevin H. Jones, Patrick Meagher, & David Sun - Curated by Ronald Jones, November 11, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Project: Defective Brick Project: Galia Solomonoff, November 11, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Project Space II: Barnaby Furnas, November 11, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - The Emperor's New Clothes: Antenna Design, January 27, 2001 (Box 68, Folder 11)